Guide to the Wilfrid S. Sellars Papers, 1899-1990 ASP.1991.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Library, V.
  - Annotated Books, dates; 1.
    - Delbos, Victor. La Philosophie Francaise. Librairie Plon, 1921 (Box 182, Item 292)
    - Sellars, Roy Wood. Critical Realism, a Study of the Nature and Conditions of Knowledge. Rand McNally & Company, 1916 (Box 182, Item 293)
    - Chevallier, Gabriel. Clochemerle, Roman. J.Ferenczi et fils, 1937 (Box 182, Item 294)
    - Grunbaum, Adolf. Philosophical Problems of Space and Time. Alfred A. Knopf, 1963 (Box 182, Item 295)
    - Ryle, Gilbert. The Concept of the Mind. Hutchinson's University Library, 1949 (Box 182, Item 296)
    - Dummett, Michael. Frege, Philosophy of Language. Gerald Duckworth & Company Limited, 1973 (Box 182, Item 297)
    - Vleeschauwer, H.J. de. La Deduction Transcendantale dans l'oeuvre de Kant. "De Sikkel", 1936 (Box 182, Item 298)
    - Heimsoeth, Heinz, Dr. Die Methode der Erkenntnis bei Descartes und Leibniz: Erste Halfte: Historische Einleitung. Descartes' Methode der klaren und deutlichen Erkenntnis. Alfred Topelmann, 1912 (Box 182, Item 299)
    - Heimsoeth, Heinz, Dr. Die Methode der Erkenntnis bei Descartes und Leibniz: Zweite Halfte: Leibniz' Methode der formalen Begrundung Erkenntnislehre und Monadologie. Alfred Topelmann, 1914 (Box 182, Item 300)
    - Hesse, Mary B. Models and Analogies in Science. Sheed and Ward, 1963 (Box 182, Item 301)
    - Davidson, Donald and Jaakko Hintikka. Words and Objections, Essays on the work of W.V. Quine. D. Reidel, 1969 (Box 182, Item 302)
    - Malcolm, Norman. Knowledge and Certainty, Essays and Lectures. Prentice-Hall, Inc., 1963 (Box 182, Item 303)
    - Hook, Sidney. John Dewey: Philosopher of Science and Freedom, A Symposium. The Dial Press, 1950 (Box 182, Item 304)
    - Wisdom, John. Problems of Mind and Matter. Cambridge at the University Press, 1934 (Box 182, Item 305)
    - Dewey, John. The Quest for Certainty: A Study of the Relation of Knowledge and Action, Gifford Lectures 1929. Capricorn Books, G.P. Putnam's Sons, 1960 (Box 182, Item 306)
    - Collingwood, R.G. The Principles of Art. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, 1938 (Box 182, Item 307)
    - Benacerraf, Paul and Hilary Putnam. Philosophy of Mathematics, Selected Readings, edited and with an introduction. Prentice-Hall, Inc., 1964 (Box 182, Item 308)
    - Moore, George Edward. Principia Ethica. Cambridge at the University Press, 1929 (Box 182, Item 309)
    - Freud, Sigm., Prof. Massenpsychologie und ich-analyse. Internationaler Psychoanalytischer, 1921 (Box 182, Item 310)
    - Kreyche, Robert J. The Critical Realism of Roy Wood Sellars, Excerpt of Dissertation submitted to the Faculty of Philosophy of the University of Ottawa in partial fulfillment for the degree of Doctor in Philosophy. The University of Ottawa, 1952 (Box 182, Item 311)
    - Gill, Brendan. Here at the New Yorker. Random House, 1975 (Box 182, Item 312)
    - Buchler, Justus. Philosophical Writings of Peirce, selected and edited with an introduction. Dover Publications, Inc., 1955 (Box 182, Item 313)
    - Abro, A.D. The Evolution of Scientific Thought, from Newton to Einstein. Dover Publications, Inc., 1950 (Box 182, Item 314)
    - Lewis, David K. Convention / A Philosophical Study. Harvard University Press, 1969 (Box 182, Item 315)
    - Boolos, George; Richard Jeffrey. Computability and Logic. Cambridge University Press, 1974 (Box 182, Item 316)
    - Korner, Stephan. Experience and Conduct, A Philosophical Enquiry into Practical Thinking. Cambridge University Press, 1976 (Box 182, Item 317)
    - Castaneda, Hector-Neri. On Philosophical Method. Nous Publications, Number 1, 1980 (Box 182, Item 318)
    - Churchman, C. West. Theory of Experimental Influence. The Macmillan Company, 1948 (Box 182, Item 319)
    - Farber, Marvin. The Foundation of Phenomenology, Edmund Husserl and the Quest for a Rigourous Science of Philosophy. Harvard University Press, 1943 (Box 182, Item 320)
    - Sharp, Frank Chapman. Ethics. The Century Co., 1928 (Box 182, Item 321)
    - Baier, Kurt. The Moral Point of View: A Rational Basis for Ethics. Cornell University Press, 1943 (Box 182, Item 322)
    - Hare, R.M. Freedom and Reason. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, 1963 (Box 182, Item 323)
    - Lewis, Clarence Irving. Our Social Inheritence. Indiana University Press, 1957 (Box 182, Item 324)
    - Stevenson, Charles L. Ethics and Language. Yale University Press, 1944 (Box 182, Item 325)
    - Blanshard, Brand. Reason and Goodness. George Allen & Unwin Ltd, 1961 (Box 182, Item 326)
    - Schlick, Moritz. Problems of Ethics. Prentice-Hall, Inc., 1939 (Box 182, Item 327)
    - Weber, Max. The Rational and Social Foundations of Music. Southern Illinois University Press, 1958 (Box 182, Item 328)
    - Ehrenzweig, Anton. The Psycho-Analysis of Artistic Vision and Hearing, An Introduction to a theory of Unconscious Perception. Routledge & Kegan Paul Ltd, 1953 (Box 182, Item 329)
    - Raphael, D. Daiches. The Moral Sense. Oxford University Press, 1947 (Box 182, Item 330)
    - Edwards, Paul. The Logic of Moral Discourse. The Free Press, 1955 (Box 182, Item 331)
    - Vaihinger, H., Dr. Commentar zu Kants Kritik der Reinen Vernunft, zum hundertjahrigen jubilaum derselben. Union Deutsche Verlagsgesellschaft, 1892 (Box 182, Item 332)
    - Feigl, Herbert, Wilfred Sellars, and Keith Lehrer. New Readings in Philosophical Analysis. Appleton-Century-Crofts Educational Division, Meredith Corporation, 1972 (Box 182, Item 333)
    - Sellars, Roy Wood. The Principles Perspectives and Problems of Philosophy. Pageant Press International Corp., 1970 (Box 182, Item 334)
    - Sellars, Roy Wood. The Philosophy of Physical Realism. Russell & Russell, 1966 (Box 182, Item 335)
    - Sellars, Roy Wood. Reflections on American Philosophy from Within. University of Notre Dame Press, 1969 (Box 182, Item 336)
    - Sellars, Roy Wood. Critical Realism, A Study of the Nature and Conditions of Knowledge. Russell & Russell, 1969 (Box 182, Item 337)
    - Witschel, Von Gunter. Wilfrid Sellars, Erkenntnistheoretische fragen untersucht auf der frundlage von "Philsophy and the Scientific Image of Man". Bouvier Verlag Herbert Grunmann, 1972 (Box 182, Item 338)
    - Moore, George Edward. Some Main Problems of Philosophy. George Allen & Unwin Ltd., 1953 (Box 182, Item 339)
    - Leyden, W. von. Locke, John: Essays on the Law of Nature, the Latin text with a translation, introduction and notes, together with transcripts of Locke's shorthand in his journal for 1676, edited. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, 1954 (Box 182, Item 340)
    - Jager, Ronald. The Development of Bertrand Russell's Philosophy. George Allen & Unwin Ltd, 1972 (Box 182, Item 341)
    - Rosenberg, Jay F. Linguistic Representation. D. Reidel Publishing Company, 1974 (Box 182, Item 342)
    - Rescher, Nicholas. Essays in Honor of Carl G. Hempel, A Tribute on the Occasion of his Sixty-Fifth Birthday, Essays by Davidson, Donald et al., edited. D. Reidel Publishing Company, 1969 (Box 182, Item 343)
    - Schafer, Lothar. Kants Metaphysik der Natur. Walter De Gruyter & Co., 1966 (Box 182, Item 344)
    - Crombie, A.C. Medieval and Early Modern Science, V.1, Science in the Middle Ages: V-XIII Centuries. Doubleday Anchor Books, 1959 (Box 182, Item 345)
    - Aiken, Henry D. Hume, David: Dialogues Concerning Natural Religion, edited with introduction. Hafner Publishing Company, 1948 (Box 182, Item 346)
    - Wolfson, Henry Austryn. The Philosophy of Spinoza. Meridian Books, 1958 (Box 182, Item 347)
    - Farrington, Benjamin. Greek Science, Its Meaning For Us, Volume 1: Thales to Aristotle. Penguin Books, 1944 (Box 182, Item 348)
    - Farrington, Benjamin. Greek Science, Its Meaning For Us, Volume II: Theophrastus to Galen. Penguin Books, 1949 (Box 182, Item 349)
    - Nikam, N.A. and Richard McKeon. The Edicts of Asoka, edited and translated. University of Chicago Press, 1959 (Box 182, Item 350)
    - Boehner, Philotheus, O.F.M. Ockham: Philosophical Writings. Thomas Nelson and Sons Ltd, 1957 (Box 182, Item 351)
    - Aiken, Henry D. Hume's Moral and Political Philosophy, edited with an introduction. Hafner Publishing Company, 1948 (Box 182, Item 352)
    - Westling, Achilles. On the Constitution of Experimental Knowledge. The Academic Book Store, 1968 (Box 182, Item 353)
    - Burch, George Bosworth. Early Medieval Philosophy. King's Crown Press, Columbia University, 1951 (Box 182, Item 354)
    - Drange, Theodore. Type Crossings, Sentential Meaninglessness in the Border Area of Linguistics and Philosophy. Mouton & Co., 1966 (Box 182, Item 355)
    - Hochberg, Herbert. Thought, Fact, and Reference, The Origins and Ontology of Logical Atomism. University of Minnesota Press, 1978 (Box 182, Item 356)
    - Bernstein, Richard J. John Dewey. Washington Square Press, Inc., 1966 (Box 182, Item 357)
    - Edwards, Paul, and Arthur Pap. A Modern Introduction to Philosophy, Readings from Classical and Contemporary Sources. The Free Press, 1965 (Box 182, Item 358)
    - Baier, Kurt. The Moral Point of View, A Rational Basis of Ethics. Random House, 1965 (Box 182, Item 359)
    - Mayeroff, Milton. On Caring. Harper & Row, 1972 (Box 182, Item 360)
    - McGuire, J.E., and Martin Tamny. Certain Philosophical Questions: Newton's Trinity Notebook. Cambridge University Press, 1983 (Box 182, Item 361)
    - Rescher, Nicholas. Essays in Philosophical Analysis. University of Pittsburgh Press, 1969 (Box 182, Item 362)
    - Schneewind, J.B. Mill, John Stuart: Mill's Essays on Literature and Society, edited, with and introduction. Collier Books, 1965 (Box 182, Item 363)
    - Schneewind, J.B. Mill, John Stuart: Mill's Ethical Writings, edited, with an introduction. Collier Books, 1965 (Box 182, Item 364)
    - Cohen, Morris R. Reason and Nature, An Essay on the Meaning of the Scientific Method. Harcourt, Brace and Company, 1931 (Box 182, Item 365)
    - Cassirer, Ernst. An Essay on Man, An Introduction to a Philosophy of Human Culture. Doubleday Anchor Books, 1953 (Box 182, Item 366)
    - Mays, W. The Philosophy of Whitehead. Collier Books, 1962 (Box 182, Item 367)
    - Smart, J.J.C. Between Science and Philosophy, An Introduction to the Philosophy of Science. Random House, 1968 (Box 182, Item 368)
    - Ayer, Alfred Jules. Language, Truth and Logic. Victor Gollancz Ltd., 1948 (Box 182, Item 369)
    - Pap, Arthur. The A Priori in Physical Theory. King's Crown Press, 1946 (Box 182, Item 370)
    - Church, F. J. Plato's Phaedo, translated, with an introduction. The Liberal Arts Press, 1951 (Box 182, Item 371)
    - Earle, William. Jaspers, Karl: Reason and Existenz, Five Lectures translated with an introduction. The Noonday Press, 1957 (Box 182, Item 372)
    - Abro, A. d'. The Rise of New Physics, its mathematical and physical theories. Dover Publications, Inc., 1951 (Box 182, Item 373)
    - Lindsay, A.D. Kant. Ernest Benn Limited, 1934 (Box 182, Item 374)
    - Morris, C.R. Locke, Berkeley, Hume. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, 1931 (Box 182, Item 375)
    - Yalden-Thomson, D.C. Hume: Theory of Knowledge, Containing the Enquiry Concerning Human Understanding, the Abstract, and selected passages from Book I of A Treatise of Human Nature, edited. University of Texas Press, 1953 (Box 182, Item 376)
    - Laski, Harold J. Political Thought in England, from Locke to Bentham. Thornton Butterworth Limited, 1920 (Box 182, Item 377)
    - Lindsay, A.D. Hume's Treatise of Human Nature, with introductions, Vol. I. J.M. Dent & Sons Ltd., 1911(?) (Box 182, Item 378)
    - Lindsay, A.D. Hume's Treatise of Human Nature, with introductions, Vol. II. J.M. Dent & Sons Ltd., 1911 (Box 182, Item 379)
    - Smith, Norman Kemp. Hume's Dialogues Concerning Natural Religion, edited with an introduction. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, 1935 (Box 182, Item 380)
    - Selby-Bigge, L.A. Hume, David: Enquiries Concerning the Human Understanding and Concerning the Principles of Morals, reprinted from the posthumous edition of 1777 and edited with introduction, comparative tables of contents, and analytic index, second edition. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, 1902 (Box 182, Item 381)
    - Smith, Thomas Vernor and William Kelley Wright. Essays in Philosophy by Seventeen Doctors of Philosophy of the University of Chicago, edited. Open Court Publishing Co., 1929 (Box 182, Item 382)
    - Adams, George P. and WM. Peppereel Montague. Contemporary American Philosophy, Personal Statements, Vol. I, edited. George Allen & Unwin Ltd, 1930 (Box 182, Item 383)
    - Vlastos, Gregory. Plato: Protagoras, Benjamin Jowett's translation, extensively revised by Martin Ostwald, edited, with an introduction. The Bobbs-Merrill Company, Inc., 1956 (Box 182, Item 384)
    - Martin, R.M. Truth & Denotation, A Study in Semantical Theory. The University of Chicago Press, 1958 (Box 182, Item 385)
    - Day, John Patrick. Inductive Probability. Routledge & Kegan Paul, 1961 (Box 182, Item 386)
    - The Mysterious Island. Franklin Edition. (Box 182, Item 387)
    - Brain, W. Russell. Mind, Perception, and Science. Blackwell Scientific Publications, 1951 (Box 182, Item 388)
    - Beckwith, Burnham P. The Economic Theory of a Socialist Economy. Stanford University Press, 1949 (Box 182, Item 389)
    - Hackforth, R. Plato's Examination of Pleasure, A Translation of the Philebus, with introduction and commentary. The Liberal Arts Press, 1945 (Box 182, Item 390)
    - Frankfurt, Harry D. Demons, Dragons, and Madmen, The Defense of Reason in Descarte's Meditations. The Bobbs-Merrill Company, Inc., 1970 (Box 182, Item 391)
    - Sellars, Roy Wood. Critical Realism, A Study of the Nature and Conditions of Knowledge. Russell & Russell, 1916 (Box 182, Item 392)
    - Von Wright, Georg H. An Essay in Modal Logic. North Holland Publishing Company, 1951 (Box 182, Item 393)
    - Helmbold, W.C. Plato's Gorgias, translated, with an introduction. The Liberal Arts Press, 1952 (Box 182, Item 394)
    - Bergmann, Gustav. Meaning and Existence. The University of Wisconsin Press, 1960 (Box 182, Item 395)
    - Warren, W. Preston. Principles of Emergent Realism, Philosophical Essays by Roy Wood Sellars, compiled and edited. Warren H. Green, Inc., 1970 (Box 182, Item 396)
    - Bluck, R.S. Plato's Phaedo, translated, with introduction, notes, and appendices. The Bobbs-Merrill Company, Inc., 1955 (Box 182, Item 397)
    - Piest, Oskar. Plato's Timaeus, translated by Francis M. Cornford and reprinted from his work, Plato's Cosmology, edited. The Liberal Arts Press, 1959 (Box 182, Item 398)
    - Cerf, Bennett A., Donald S. Klopper. The Complete Works of Homer, The Iliad done into English Prose by Lang, Andrew et al., The Odyssey done into English Prose by Butcher, S.H. et al. The Modern Library (Box 182, Item 399)
    - Scott, Theodore Kermit. John Buridan: Sophisms on Meaning and Truth, translated and with an introduction. Appleton-Century-Crofts, 1966 (Box 182, Item 400)
    - Clark, Gordon H. Selections from Hellenistic Philosophy. F.S. Crofts & Co., 1940 (Box 182, Item 401)
    - Leonard, W.E. Lucretius: On the Nature of Things, a metrical translation. J.M. Dent & Sons Ltd, 1921 (Box 182, Item 402)
    - Church, F.J. Plato: Phaedo, translated by F.J. Church, with an introduction by Fulton H. Anderson. The Bobbs-Merrill Company, Inc., 1951 (Box 182, Item 403)
    - Schlipp, Paul Arthur. The Philosophy of Rudolf Carnap, edited. Open Court, 1963 (Box 182, Item 404)
    - Reichenbach, Hans. Elements of Symbolic Logic. The Macmillan Company, 1947 (Box 182, Item 405)
    - Prange, Gordon W. Target Tokyo, the Story of the Sorge Spy Ring. McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1984 (Box 182, Item 406)
    - Browning, Douglas. Philosophers of Process, edited by Douglas Browning with an introduction by Charles Hartshorne. Random House, 1965 (Box 182, Item 407)
    - Dennett, D.C. Content and Consciousness. Routledge & Kegan Paul, 1969 (Box 182, Item 408)
    - Armstrong, D.M. Bodily Sensations. Routledge & Kegan Paul, 1962 (Box 182, Item 409)
    - Cattell, Raymond B. An Introduction to Personality Study. Hutchinson's University Library, 1950 (Box 182, Item 410)
    - Rorty, Richard. The Linguistic Turn, Recent Essays in Philosophical Method, edited and with an introduction. The University of Chicago Press, 1967 (Box 182, Item 411)
    - Chattopadhyaya, Debiprasad. Individuals and Societies, A Methodological Inquiry. Scientific Book Agency, 1975 (Box 182, Item 412)
    - Beck, Lewis White. Kant, Immanuel: Prologomena to any Future Metaphysics, with an introduction. The Bobbs-Merrill Company, Inc., 1950 (Box 182, Item 413)
    - Heidigger, Martin. Husserl, Edmund: The Phenomenology of Internal Time-Consciousness, edited by Martin Heidegger, Tranlated by James S. Churchill, Introduction by Calvin O. Schrag. Indiana University Press, 1964 (Box 182, Item 414)
    - Farber, Martin. Philosophic Though in France and the United States, Essays Representing Major Trends in Contemporary French and American Philosophy, edited. University of Buffalo Publications in Philosophy, 1950 (Box 182, Item 415)
    - Northrop, F.S.C. and Henry Margenau, Co-Chairmen. The Nature of Concepts, Their Inter-Relation and Role in Social Structure. Proceedings of the Stillwater Conference, 1950 (June 6-9) (Box 182, Item 416)
    - Puntel, L. Bruno. Wahrheitstheorien in der Neueren Philosophie. Wissenschaftliche Buchegesellschaft, 1978 (Box 182, Item 417)
    - Weyl, Hermann. Philosophie der Mathematik und Naturwissenschaft. R. Oldenbourg, 1928 (Box 182, Item 418)
    - Flaubert, Gustave. Madame Bovary, edited by Lucas Lexow. J.H. Sears & Company, Inc., n.d. (Box 182, Item 419)
    - Smith, Norman Kemp. Immanuel Kant's Critique of Pure Reason, translated. Macmillan & Co., Limited, 1952 (Box 182, Item 420)
    - Kvart, Igal. A Theory of Counterfactuals. Hackett Publishing Company, 1986 (Box 182, Item 421)
    - Musset, Alfred de. Comedies et Proverbes, tome deuxieme. Nelson, n.d. (Box 182, Item 422)
    - Jeffreys, Harold. Scientific Inference. Cambridge at the University Press, 1937 (Box 182, Item 423)
    - Sellars, R.W. The Essentials of Logic. Houghton Mifflin Company, 1945 (Box 182, Item 424)
    - Men and Machines, the Symposia Read at the Joint Session of the Aristotelian Society and Mind Association at Birmingham, July 11-13, 1952. Harrison and Sons, Ltd. (Box 182, Item 425)
    - Strawson, P.F. Introduction to Logical Theory. Methuen & Co. Ltd., 1952 (Box 182, Item 426)
    - Russell, Bertrand. The Problems of Philosophy. Oxford University Press, 1912 (Box 182, Item 427)
    - Piest, Oskar. Mill, John Stuart: Utilitarianism, edited. The Liberal Arts Press, 1949 (Box 182, Item 428)
    - Wubnig, Judy. Martin, Gottfried: Arithmetic and Combinatorics, translated and edited. Southern Illinois University Press, 1985 (Box 182, Item 429)
    - Sapir, Edward. Language, an Introduction to the Study of Speech. Harcourt, Brace and Company, 1921 (Box 182, Item 430)
    - Prior A.N. Formal Logic. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, 1955 (Box 182, Item 431)
    - Dennett, Daniel C. Brainstorms, Philosophical Essays on Mind and Psychology. Bradford Books, 1978 (Box 182, Item 432)
    - Nagel, Ernest et al. Logic, Methodology, and Philosophy of Science, Proceedings of the 1960 International Conference. Stanford University Press, 1962 (Box 182, Item 433)
    - Hospers, John. Libertarianism, A Political Philosophy for Tomorrow. Reason Press, 1970 (Box 182, Item 434)
    - Szczesny, Gerhard. Club Voltaire, Jahrbook fur kritische Aufklarung IV, herausgegeben von. Rowohlt, 1970 (Box 182, Item 435)
    - Warren, W. Preston. Roy Wood Sellars. Twayne Publishers, 1975 (Box 182, Item 436)
    - Wilkerson, T.E. Kant's Critique of Pure Reason, A Commentary for Students. Clarendon Press, 1976 (Box 182, Item 437)
    - Collingwood, R.G. The Principles of Art. A Galaxy Book, Oxford University Press, 1958 (Box 182, Item 438)
    - Carritt, E.F. What is Beauty? A First Introduction to the Subject and to Modern Theories. Oxford at the University Press, 1958 (Box 182, Item 439)
    - Wimsatt, W.K., Jr. The Verbal Icon, Studies in the Meaning of Poetry. The Noonday Press, 1958 (Box 182, Item 440)
    - Rollins, C.D. Knowledge and Experience, Proceedings of the 1962 Oberlin Colloquium in Philosophy, edited. University of Pittsburgh Press (Box 182, Item 441)
    - Mischel, Theodore. Human Action, Conceptual and Empirical Issues, edited. Academic Press, 1969 (Box 182, Item 442)
    - Gale, Richard M. The Language of Time. Routledge & Kegan Paul, 1968 (Box 182, Item 443)
    - Copi, Irving M. and James A. Gould. Contemporary Readings in Logical Theory. The Macmillan Company, 1967 (Box 182, Item 444)
    - Smart, J.J.C. Philosophy and Scientific Realism. Routledge & Kegan Paul, 1963 (Box 182, Item 445)
    - Smart, J.J.C. An Outline of a System of Utilitarian Ethics. Melbourne University Press, 1961 (Box 182, Item 446)
    - Morris, Mary. The Philosophical Writings of Leibniz, selected and translated. J.M. Dent & Sons Ltd., 1934 (Box 182, Item 447)
    - Danto, Arthur C. Analytical Philosophy of History. Cambridge at the University Press, 1965 (Box 182, Item 448)
    - Blanshard, Brand. Reason and Analysis. George Allen & Unwin Ltd., 1962 (Box 182, Item 449)
    - Sellars, Wilfred. Science, Perception and Reality. Routledge & Kegan Paul, 1963 (Box 182, Item 450)
    - Feigl, Herbert, et al. New Readings in Philosophical Analysis, edited. Appleton-Century-Crofts, 1972 (Box 182, Item 451)
    - Smith, Norman Kemp. Immanuel Kant's Critique of Pure Reason, translated, unabridged edition. St. Martin's Press, 1965 (Box 182, Item 452)
    - Rescher, Nicholas. Galen and the Syllogism. University of Pittsburgh Press, 1966 (Box 182, Item 453)
    - Mourelatos, Alexander P.D. The Route of Parmenides, A Study of Word, Image, and Argument in the Fragments. Yale University Press, 1970 (Box 182, Item 454)
    - Cornman, James W. Metaphysics, Reference, and Language. Yale University Press, 1966 (Box 182, Item 455)
    - Hartnack, Justus. Philosophical Problems, A Modern Introduction. Munksgaard, 1962 (Box 182, Item 456)
    - Khatchadourian, Haig. A Critical Study in Method. Martinus Nijhoff, 1967 (Box 182, Item 457)
    - Carnap, Rudolf. Foundations of Logic and Mathematics. University of Chicago Press, 1939 (Box 182, Item 458)
    - Pepper, Stephen C. Concept and Quality, A World Hypothesis. Open Court, 1967 (Box 182, Item 459)
    - Fodor, Jerry A. and Jerrold J. Katz. The Structure of Language, Readings in the Philosophy of Language. Prentice-Hall, Inc., 1964 (Box 182, Item 460)
    - Benacerraf, Paul and Hilary Putnam. Philosophy of Mathematics, selected readings, edited and with an introduction. Prentice-Hall, Inc., 1964 (Box 182, Item 461)
    - Van Fraasen, Bas C. Formal Semantics and Logic. The Macmillan Company, 1971 (Box 182, Item 462)
    - The Most of P.G. Wodehouse. Simon and Schuster, 1960 (Box 182, Item 463)
    - Cherniss, Harold. The Riddle of the Early Academy. University of California Press, 1945 (Box 182, Item 464)
    - Mehlberg, Henryk. The Reach of Science. University of Toronto Press, 1958 (Box 182, Item 465)
    - Rescher, Nicholas. The Coherence Theory of Truth. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, 1973 (Box 182, Item 466)
    - Grossman, Reinhardt. Reflections on Frege's Philosophy. Northwestern University Press, 1969 (Box 182, Item 467)
    - Cornman, James W. Perception, Common Sense, and Science. Yale University Press, 1975 (Box 182, Item 468)
    - Cecil, David. Max, A Biography. Houghton Mifflin Company, 1965 (Box 182, Item 469)
    - Cassidy, Vincent H. The Sea Around Them, The Atlantic Ocean, A.D. 1250. Louisiana State University Press, 1968 (Box 182, Item 470)
    - Hare, R.M. Essays on Philosophical Method. Macmillan, 1971 (Box 182, Item 471)
    - Rosenberg, Jay F. Linguistic Representation. Draft copy, 1973 (Box 182, Item 472)